Neroslyk Maxum

Unity Developer

ABOUT

I am a university student majoring in Computer Science. I don't have much work experience yet, but there are other qualitative advantages. I am very attentive and responsible. At the university, I did various IT projects to order, so I have no problems in working with clients and I do everything right on time. Also, because of this, I learn quickly and can handle any task. At the university I finish the military department, the head of the group.

SKILLS

Experience with Unity C# Experience with .Net C# Experience with C++ Experience with Java Experience with Dart and Flutter Experience with HTML, CSS, JS Experience working with Blender Ability to work with databases Ability to model in low-poly Knowledge of SOLID principles Ability to publish finished projects The ability to add third-party SDKs to projects The ability to work in a team Multitasking Stress resistance Attention to detail

CONTACT INFORMATION

Address: str. Akademika Yangelya, 5, Kyiv, Ukraine, 03056

Email: maxum_neroslyk@ukr.net Phone: +38 (066) 703-39-16 LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/wiziks Portfolio: wiziks.github.io

EXPERIENCE

Teacher at an IT school

"IT FRIENDS" | August 2021 - Present time

- Creating a program for learning Unity and WEB
 Teaching material for children according to the created program
- Close teamwork with administrators, other teachers
- Close connection with children and their parents

No-Code Developer

"One Reach" | August 2022 - September 2022

- Creating custom bot solutions for solving real-world problems
 Developing new features and functionality to increase the capacity of OneReach.ai platform
 Participating in estimation and planning sessions of Solution Builders team

Freelancer

"Computer Science" | October 2020 - May 2022

- Create course projects in C++ and C# programming languages, to which relational databases are connected Do laboratory work for the specialty "Computer Science" in C#, C++, Java, Flutter
- Create one-page sites
 Develop simple programming languages

EDUCATION

National Technical University of Ukraine "Kyiv Polytechnic Institute named after Igor Sikorsky"

Bachelor | September 2019 - Present time

Major: 122, computer science

CERTIFICATES

Course "Basics of creating games on Unity"

Term: 2021-2022 Certificate: surl.li/cmfga